{
    "subject": "resource/Eyewitness_(TV_series)",
    "predicate": "ontology/company",
    "object": "resource/Time-Life_Television",
    "human_readable": "Eyewitness is a TV series produced by Time-Life Television.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9257377982139587,
            "question": "Who produced the TV series 'Eyewitness'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5389699339866638,
            "question": "What type of program is 'Eyewitness'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41728946566581726,
            "question": "Is 'Eyewitness' a fictional or non-fictional show?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38711661100387573,
            "question": "What makes the TV series 'Eyewitness' unique compared to other documentaries or factual programs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3710744380950928,
            "question": "Are there any notable actors or personalities associated with 'Eyewitness'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3704695403575897,
            "question": "Is there a streaming service where you can currently watch 'Eyewitness'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3013364374637604,
            "question": "What was the focus of each episode in 'Eyewitness'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2416190356016159,
            "question": "What is the name of the TV series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.234485924243927,
            "question": "When did 'Eyewitness' air originally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1960410475730896,
            "question": "Was 'Eyewitness' popular during its original run?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eyewitness is a TV series produced by Time-Life Television.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4400_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did 'Eyewitness' air originally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4400_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the TV series?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4400_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the focus of each episode in 'Eyewitness'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4400_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4400_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4400_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4400_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4400_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4400_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4400_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4400_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4400_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4400_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4400_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that \"Eyewitness\" was produced by BBC and DK Vision. There is no mention of Time-Life Television.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention Time-Life Television as the producer of the TV series Eyewitness. The correct information from the documents is that Eyewitness was produced by Dorling Kindersley Vision and BBC Wildvision, among others."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not mention any information about \"Eyewitness\" being produced by Time-Life Television. Instead, the context indicates that \"Eyewitness\" has been produced by BBC and DK Vision, among others."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}